Chapters one through nine review and expansion how and what to do So you're in
a tough relationship with English. Let's talk about that Maybe you've tried to pick
up an American accent before and it made you uncomfortable Maybe your family thinks
that you shouldn't change. Maybe you've tried and failed now. You're frustrated
Whatever the reason you've got an unsatisfying relationship with English.
We're here to fix that Let's get your head in the right place. Learning a whole
language is indeed a big deal, but you've already done all the heavy lifting, having
learned the grammar and vocabulary. Right now, we're just doing the fine-tuning and
working on your accent. Here's what you should expect after the first one to six
weeks, depending on your diligence.
Hello, my name is Rie Matsubara. I am taking American accent training. Hello, my
name is Rie Matsubara. I am taking American accent training. Hello, my name
is Manuel Rojas. I am taking American accent training. Hello, my name is Manuel.
I'm taking American accent training. Hello, my name is Callie Lu.
Hello, my name is Kelly Luh, I'm taking American accent training. Hello, my name
is Raymond Chun, I'm taking American accent training. Hello, my name is Raymond
Chun, I'm taking American accent training. Hello, my name is Narachem, I'm taking
American accent training. Hello, my name is Naz, I'm taking American accent
training.